<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Solve It</string>
    <string name="version">1.0.0</string>
    <string name="illustration00">Having trouble solving questions at home,\n and you just need a worked out solution to\nget back on track ?</string>
    <string name="illustration01">Simply snap a picture of the question you\nwant to solve\n </string>
    <string name="illustration02">Add a few text and upload the question\n\n</string>
    <string name="illustration03">Let the community solve the question\nfor you\n</string>
    <string name="illustration04">Receive your answer\n\n</string>
    <string name="illustration05">Solve questions and get paid\n\n</string>

    <!-- payments -->
    <string name="paynow_five_url">https://www.paynow.co.zw/Payment/Link/?q=c2VhcmNoPXJicnlhbmJlbiU0MGdtYWlsLmNvbSZhbW91bnQ9NS4wMCZyZWZlcmVuY2U9WU9VYXJlQVdFU09NRSZsPTA%3d</string>

    <!-- genders -->
    <string-array name="array_gender">
        <item>male</item>
        <item>female</item>
        <item>rather not say</item>
    </string-array>

    <!-- sort -->
    <string-array name="sort_items">
        <item>Date</item>
        <item>Votes</item>
    </string-array>

    <!-- Education levels -->
    <string-array name="array_education">
        <item>Primary-education</item>
        <item>O-level</item>
        <item>A-level</item>
        <item>Higher-education</item>
    </string-array>

    <!-- terms and conditions -->
    <string name="we_can_t_stress_this_enough_a_tc_isn_t_mandatory_but_you_should_treat_it_like_it_is_here_s_why_you_can_decide_which_country_s_laws_apply_to_govern_the_agreement_this_is_otherwise_known_as_choosing_the_jurisdiction_you_will_generally_choose_the_country_where_the_website_or_business_is_based_you_can_remove_or_delete_abusive_accounts_for_example_say_you_run_a_social_media_platform_and_explain_that_people_who_post_inflammatory_abusive_or_explicit_content_will_be_blocked_from_the_service_someone_posts_abusive_content_you_can_block_their_account_without_worry_because_you_can_rely_on_your_terms_and_conditions_agreement_you_can_limit_your_responsibility_you_can_include_disclaimer_clauses_in_your_agreement_that_say_you_re_not_liable_for_third_party_content_and_you_don_t_endorse_it_you_can_also_say_that_you_re_not_responsible_for_mistakes_and_typos_or_content_uploaded_by_users_which_other_users_may_find_offensive_you_can_manage_a_user_s_expectations_of_your_website_or_platform_when_the_terms_are_clear_users_know_what_they_can_and_cannot_expect_from_you_you_can_set_your_own_site_rules_and_the_consequences_for_violating_these_rules_within_legal_limits_you_can_t_contract_out_of_certain_rules_such_as_the_law_of_negligence_it_s_vital_that_you_protect_your_intellectual_property_rights_by_setting_out_what_your_rights_are_in_the_terms_and_conditions_agreement_you_can_take_action_against_users_who_infringe_your_rights_it_should_be_clear_that_the_logo_brand_and_content_belong_to_you_creating_a_terms_and_conditions_agreement_creating_a_terms_and_conditions_agreement_when_you_begin_to_draft_a_terms_and_conditions_agreement_there_are_certain_clauses_you_should_make_sure_to_include_let_s_look_at_each_of_these_clauses_in_turn_and_consider_how_they_are_drafted_introduction_clauses_it_s_very_helpful_to_set_out_a_clause_or_clauses_at_the_very_beginning_of_the_agreement_explaining_what_the_agreement_is_who_it_applies_to_and_when_the_terms_are_triggered_here_s_how_instagram_does_this_it_notes_that_the_terms_are_triggered_when_a_user_creates_an_account_on_the_platform_or_uses_the_app_and_it_clearly_states_that_the_terms_constitute_an_agreement_between_instagram_and_the_user_instagram_terms_of_use_intro_clause_it_s_important_to_clarify_who_the_agreement_applies_to_since_it_s_legally_binding_youtube_for_example_makes_it_clear_that_users_must_agree_to_the_terms_before_using_the_service_anyone_who_uses_their_service_is_assumed_to_agree_to_the_terms_some_people_are_legally_prohibited_from_entering_into_the_agreement_youtube_terms_of_service_accepting_the_terms_clause_this_clause_is_placed_close_to_the_beginning_of_the_agreement_and_is_part_of_the_introductory_clauses_who_can_use_your_platform_although_it_s_illegal_to_discriminate_against_people_based_on_protected_characteristics_such_as_their_gender_sexual_orientation_or_ethnicity_it_is_perfectly_reasonable_to_put_certain_restrictions_on_who_can_use_your_website_or_app_instagram_for_example_prohibits_children_under_the_age_of_13_from_creating_accounts_it_also_bans_convicted_sex_offenders_significantly_instagram_also_bans_users_from_returning_to_the_site_if_their_profile_is_deleted_or_blocked_the_clause_is_simple_but_effective_to_include_in_its_terms_instagram_terms_of_use_who_can_use_instagram_restrictions_clause_helpfully_instagram_establishes_why_the_restrictions_exist_they_want_to_comply_with_the_law_and_promote_a_safe_inclusive_platform_we_recommend_including_reasons_like_these_for_your_own_clauses_unacceptable_behavior_clause_these_clauses_address_what_behavior_is_unacceptable_on_your_website_they_are_an_opportunity_to_set_out_the_rules_that_you_expect_users_to_abide_by_and_what_the_consequences_will_be_if_the_user_violates_these_rules_it_s_helpful_to_set_out_specific_examples_of_behavior_that_violates_your_site_rules_the_oath_terms_of_service_sets_out_the_behavior_that_it_deems_unacceptable_it_uses_broad_language_such_as">...We can\'t stress this enough - a TC isn\'t mandatory, but you should treat it like it is. Here\'s why. You can decide which country\'s laws apply to govern the agreement. This is otherwise known as choosing the jurisdiction. You will generally choose the country where the website, or business, is based. You can remove or delete abusive accounts. For example, say you run a social media platform and explain that people who post inflammatory, abusive, or explicit content will be blocked from the service. Someone posts abusive content. You can block their account without worry, because you can rely on your Terms and Conditions agreement. You can limit your responsibility. You can include disclaimer clauses in your agreement that say you\'re not liable for third party content, and you don\'t endorse it. You can also say that you\'re not responsible for mistakes and typos, or content uploaded by users which other users may find offensive. You can manage a user\'s expectations of your website or platform. When the terms are clear, users know what they can and cannot expect from you. You can set your own site rules and the consequences for violating these rules, within legal limits. You can\'t contract out of certain rules such as the law of negligence. It\'s vital that you protect your intellectual property rights. By setting out what your rights are in the Terms and Conditions agreement, you can take action against users who infringe your rights. It should be clear that the logo, brand, and content belong to you. Creating a Terms and Conditions Agreement Creating a Terms and Conditions Agreement When you begin to draft a Terms and Conditions agreement, there are certain clauses you should make sure to include. Let\'s look at each of these clauses in turn and consider how they are drafted. Introduction Clauses It\'s very helpful to set out a clause (or clauses) at the very beginning of the agreement explaining what the agreement is, who it applies to, and when the terms are triggered. Here\'s how Instagram does this. It notes that the terms are triggered when a user creates an account on the platform or uses the app, and it clearly states that the terms constitute an agreement between Instagram and the user: Instagram Terms of Use: Intro clause It\'s important to clarify who the agreement applies to since it\'s legally binding. YouTube, for example, makes it clear that: Users must agree to the terms before using the service Anyone who uses their service is assumed to agree to the terms Some people are legally prohibited from entering into the agreement YouTube Terms of Service: Accepting the Terms clause This clause is placed close to the beginning of the agreement and is part of the introductory clauses. Who Can Use Your Platform Although it\'s illegal to discriminate against people based on protected characteristics such as their gender, sexual orientation, or ethnicity, it is perfectly reasonable to put certain restrictions on who can use your website or app. Instagram, for example, prohibits children under the age of 13 from creating accounts. It also bans convicted sex offenders. Significantly, Instagram also bans users from returning to the site if their profile is deleted or blocked. The clause is simple but effective to include in its terms. Instagram Terms of Use: Who Can Use Instagram - Restrictions clause Helpfully, Instagram establishes why the restrictions exist - they want to comply with the law and promote a safe, inclusive platform. We recommend including reasons like these for your own clauses. Unacceptable Behavior Clause These clauses address what behavior is unacceptable on your website. They are an opportunity to set out the rules that you expect users to abide by, and what the consequences will be if the user violates these rules. It\'s helpful to set out specific examples of behavior that violates your site rules. The Oath Terms of Service sets out the behavior that it deems unacceptable. It uses broad language such as</string>

</resources>